New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board Decisions 5319
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board Decisions
1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board
5319
13 cubic feet
13 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Decisions of the New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board.
5621943
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 27, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection is boxes 64 through 76 of the NYS Unemployment Insurance Board Decisions. For boxes 1-63 see collection 5376.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5376: New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board Decisions 5379: Wisconsin Unemployment Compensation Department Miscellaneous Tables
Unemployment insurance -- New York (State); New York (State). Unemployment Insurance Appeal Board
5621943
- 266,000 - 280,000 (Box 64)
  - 266000, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - 267000, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - 268000, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - 269000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - 270000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - 271000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - 272000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - 273000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - 274000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - 275000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - 276000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - 277000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - 278000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - 279000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - 280000, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- 281,000 - 296,000 (Box 65)
  - 281000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - 282000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - 283000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - 284000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - 285000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - 286000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - 287000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - 288000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - 289000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - 290000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - 291000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - 292000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - 293000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - 294000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - 295000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - 296000, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Wins, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- 297,000 - 307,000 (Box 66)
  - 297000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - 298000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - 299000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - 300000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - 301000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - 302000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - 303000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - 304000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - 305000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - 306000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - 307000, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Wins, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- 308,000 - 325,000 (Box 67)
  - 308000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - 309000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - 310000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - 311000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - 312000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - 313000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - 314000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - 315000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - 316000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - 317000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - 318000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - 319000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - 320000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - 321000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - 322000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - 323000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - 324000, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - 325000-325999, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- 343000-343999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- 342000-342999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- 341000-341999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- 340000-340999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- 339000-339498, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- 339503-339999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- 338000-338999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- 337507-337999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- 337000-337498, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- 336000-336999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- 335000-335999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- 334000-334999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- 333000-333999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- 332000-332999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- 331000-331999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- 330000-330999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- 329000-329999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- 328000-328999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- 327000-327999, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- 323000-326967, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- 225000-312000, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 21)
- 357,000-357,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- 356,000-356,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- 355,000-355,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- 354,000-354,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- 353,000-353,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- 352,000-352,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- 351,505-351,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- 351,000-351,497, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- 350,000-359,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- 349,000-349,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- 348,000-348,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- 347,000-347,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- 346,000-346,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- 345,000-345,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- 344,000-344,999, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- 358,000-359,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- 360,000-361,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- 361,000-361,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- 362,000-362,499, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- 362,500-362,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- 363,000-363,499, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- 363,500-363,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- 364,000-364,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- 364,500-364,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- 365,000-365,499, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- 365,000-365,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- 366,000-366,499, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- 366,500-366,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- 367,000-367,499, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- 367,500-367,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- 368,000-368,499, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- 368,500-368,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- 369,000-369,499, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- 369,500-369,999, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- 378,000-378,999, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- 377,000-377,999, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- 376,000-376,999, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- 375,000-375,999, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- 374,000-374,999, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- 373,000-373,999, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- 372,000-372,999, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- 371,000-371,999, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- 370,000-370,999, 1979 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- 388,000, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- 387,000, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- 386,000, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- 385,000, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- 384,000, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- 383,000, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- 382,000, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- 381,000, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- 380,000, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- 379,999, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- 397,000, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- 396,000, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- 395,000, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- 394,000, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- 393,000, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- 392,000, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- 391,000, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- 390,000, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- 389,000, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- 410, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- 409, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- 408, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- 407, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- 406, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- 405, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- 404,000-404,999, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- 403,000-403,999, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- 402,000-402,999, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- 401,000-401,999, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- 400,000, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- 399,000 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- 398,000, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- unfillable, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Win Appeals, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- 943,000-943,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- 942,000-942,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- 941,000-941,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- 940,000, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- 939,000-939,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- 939,000-938,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- 937,000-937,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- 936,000-936,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- 935,000-935,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- 929,000-929,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- 928,000-928,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 13)
- 927,000-927,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 14)
- 926,000-926,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 15)
- 925,000-925,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- 924,000-924,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 17)
- 923,000-923,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 18)
- 922,000-922,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 19)
- 921,000-921,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 20)
- 920,000-920,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 21)
- 914,000-917,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 22)
- 907,000-907,999, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 23)
- Appeals 363035; 363174; 363398A; 363866 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Appeals - 401015-401884 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 22)
- Appeals - 400097-400936 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 21)
- Appeals - 399148; 399181; 399196; 399209; 399264; 399265; 399497; 399534; 399552; 399818; 399904 (Box 76, Folder 20)
- Appeals - 398052; 398292; 398573; 398601; 398879; 398920; 398970 (Box 76, Folder 19)
- Appeals - 397022; 397166; 397230; 397843; 397960 (Box 76, Folder 18)
- Appeals - 369018-369996 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 17)
- Appeals - 368034-368990 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Appeals - 367004; 367017A; 367042; 367065; 367127; 367152; 367234; 367261; 367385; 367428-433; 367457; 367692; 367815; 367818; 367837; 367504 (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Appeals - 366091; 366184; 366195; 366290; 366298A; 366313; 366332; 366419; 366618; 366728; 366732; 366898A; 366990-994 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- Decisions (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Appeals - 364261; 364317; 364547; 364575; 364655; 364659A; 364688; 364703A; 364793; 364938 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Appeals - 404083-404999 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 25)
- Appeals 362081; 362166; 362221; 362249; 362914 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Appeals - 361160; 361359 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Appeals - 360620; 360959 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Appeals - 351236-359624 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Appeals - 340529-349981 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Appeals - 317496; 330394-339958 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Appeals - 265741; 299620; 310477; 316414; 316382A; 318108; 319570; 325492; 369176 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Appeal 187394 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Uncategorized (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Appeals - 365106-111; 365429; 365721; 365750; 365752; 365999 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Appeals - 915002-915997 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 35)
- Appeals - 927050-927915 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 46)
- Appeals - 926134-926955 (Box 76, Folder 45)
- Appeals - 925068-925777 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 44)
- Appeals - 924026-924977 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 43)
- Appeals - 923213-923997 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 42)
- Appeals - 922016-922967 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 41)
- Appeals - 921180-921990 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 40)
- Appeals - 920222-920987 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 39)
- Appeals - 918093-918863 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 38)
- Appeals - 402012-402997 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 23)
- Appeals - 916006-916982 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 36)
- Appeals - 403052 -403987 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 24)
- Appeals - 914061-914991 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 34)
- Appeals - 907005A-907843 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 33)
- Appeals - 906000-906869 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 32)
- Appeals - 905032-905991 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 31)
- Appeals - 904018-904988 (Box 76, Folder 30)
- Appeals - 903004-903954 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 29)
- Appeals - 902050-902989 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 28)
- Appeals - 901679-901978 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 27)
- Appeals - 405040-405992 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 26)
- Appeals - 928000-928567 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 47)
- Appeals - 917018-917990 (not complete) (Box 76, Folder 37)